...and paint symbols
on Bernadette's naked body.
(Amy:)So that's happening.
Yeah, sure, sure. Vegas is fun too. Heh.
(Amy:)I feel like crying.
Of course, I could be hormonal.
(Amy:)Oh, wait.
Maybe our menses are finally syncing up.
(Amy:)- Bernadette? No? Penny?
- Sorry.
- Really?
- Okay, yeah.
(Amy:)Yay!
Maid of honor Amy Farrah Fowler's...
(Amy:)...amazing behind-the-scenes
wedding video...
(Amy:)...take one.
(Bernadette:)We're just trying on dresses.
Do we really need to record this?
I'm sorry, are you the maid of honor?
(Bernadette:)I am the bride.
(Amy:)So no. And action.
- What do you think?
- I love it.
(Amy:)What are you, a nun?
(Amy:)Come on, bestie,
Iet's see some skin.
Oh, Amy, looking sexy.
(Bernadette:)Oh.
(Penny:)Bernadette, you look beautiful.
(Bernadette:)You do.
- Thank you.
(Amy:)Not Penny beautiful, but beautiful.
(Amy:)Come on, bestie, you're up.
(Penny(off):)Give me a minute.
(Amy:)What is taking you so long?
Oh, Amy, get the hell out of here.
Sorry, sorry. Oh, God.
(Bernadette:)- Amy!
- Sorry!